thissongissick.com 2016-11-19

# PRIVACY POLICY This policy was last modified on February 1, 2016

                          PRIVACY POLICY
This policy was last modified on February 1, 2016
The web site you have entered thissongissick.com, its sub-domains
and any services available therefrom, including any mobile versions
of the web site or mobile applications) (the “Site”) is
operated by VaynerStudios, LLC (d/b/a VaynerPublishing) (the
“Company”, “we” or “us”). We respect the your privacy rights and
recognize the importance of protecting information collected from
you and about you. This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”)
describes how we collect, use, and share that information. Your
use of the Site constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy
Policy.
1.    Collection of Information
      a.   We collect personally identifiable information when you
voluntarily provide it to us.
We collect personally identifiable information from you in several
different ways on the Site. Personally identifiable information means
information that can reasonably used to identify you personally, such as
your name, username(s), birth date, phone number, and email address).
We collect such information when you voluntarily provide it to us (such
as when you complete an online account registration, subscription form,
contest or sweepstakes entry or comment submission). You can choose
not to provide the requested information, but you might not be able to
take advantage of certain Site features.
      b. We automatically collect information about your browser
or device, your use of the Site, and your browsing or search history
when you interact with us.
      When you access and use the Site, our technology and tools
automatically collect and record certain non-personally identifiable

information about your use of the Site (including your IP address, your
browser type, the make and model of device used to view the Site,
location information, unique device identifiers, and other information
relating to your use of the Site, browser or device).
      We also use cookies, pixels, web beacons, device or HTML5 local
storage and caching, java script and other similar technologies to collect
information about your use of and access to the Site, content or
advertisements you view, and related to your activities on the Internet.
Cookies are small bits of information that may be placed on your
computer by web sites you visit, applications you use, or advertisements
you view. Cookies alone tell us nothing about who you are, unless you
or a third-party gives us personally identifiable information, which may
then be linked to the data stored in the cookie. Pixels (or pixel tags, web
beacons or clear GIFs) are small blocks of code placed on a web page or
application that read and place cookies and transmit certain information,
such as a browser or device’s IP address, when and how often the pixel
was viewed, an identifier associated with the browser or device, or the
type of browser being used.
      Further, we may work with certain third-party companies,
including those integrated with our Site, that use techniques other than
HTTP cookies to recognize your computer or device and/or to collect
and record information about your web surfing activity across multiple
platforms or devices. Please keep in mind that your web browser may
not permit you to block the use of these cross-platform or cross-device
techniques, and those browser settings that block conventional cookies
may have no effect on such techniques.
      c.    Third-parties may also automatically collect information
about you.
      Some advertisements or embedded content on the Site are served
by third-party advertising companies or third-party content providers.
Please note that these companies may also use cookies, pixels or other

similar technologies to collect information about you, both on the Site
and throughout the Internet. We do not have control over third-party
information collection and use.
      d. We may build a profile about you based on information
you voluntarily provide us, information we automatically collect
from you, and information obtained from third-parties.
      We may combine information provided by or collected from you in
connection with your use of the Site with information provided by you
to us in other ways, information we obtain from third-party market
researchers, information provided to us via your use of social media
platforms, public information or other third-party information sources.
      e.    Cross Tracking. As noted above, we may use technologies
or alternative techniques that obtain information about you, through your
web-based activities (including you use of the Site) across multiple
devices. As noted above, please keep in mind that your web browser
may not permit you to block the use of these cross-platform or cross-
device techniques, and those browser settings that block conventional
cookies may have no effect on such techniques. As we discussed, we
will use this information to provide targeting advertising services to you
and, potentially, other services that are personalized and geared to you as
further identified in this Policy.
2.    Use of Collected Information
We collect and use the types of information described above to assist in
the administration and operation of the Site and to provide you an
efficient, meaningful, and customized experience. We may use the
information to:
   • Fulfill our obligations with respect to reason you volunteered the
      information (e.g., to respond to an inquiry, administer a contest or
      sweepstakes, deliver a newsletter, etc.);

   •  Allow you to participate in interactive features of the Site;
   •  Deliver marketing, advertising, and promotional messages to you;
   •  Improve the Site or our products and services;
   •  Optimize your experience on the Site (e.g., troubleshooting
      technical programs, storing your preferences, etc.);
   • Show you relevant Site content and advertising on and off the Site,
      and analyze Site content and advertising;
   • Notify you about changes to the Site or our services (including this
      Privacy Policy); and
   • Carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from
      arrangements between you and us.
3.    Advertising
We use collected information to serve relevant, customized advertising
to you. Such advertising (and analysis of advertising) may be conducted
by us or third-parties. Your information may be shared with third-parties
for advertising delivery, contextual advertising and reporting on such
advertising. Generally, these third-parties do not have the right to use
this information beyond the scope needed to execute or support
advertising.
Some advertisers and services we use to deliver advertising may be
engaging in online behavioral advertising and interest-based advertising.
You can read more about online behavioral, interest-based advertising,
and related practices here:
   • Network Advertising Initiative:
      http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-
      advertising
   • Digital Advertising Alliance: http://www.aboutads.info/
   • Interactive Advertising Bureau: http://www.iab.net/
4.    Third-Party Websites and Third-Party Embedded Content.

We do not control the privacy policies of third-party web sites, our
affiliates, and business partners which may be accessed, directly or
indirectly, through your use of the Site. Any information you provide to,
or that is collected by, third-party sites may be subject to the privacy
policies of those sites (including third-party content embedded on the
Site), if any. It is up to you to review the terms of use and privacy
policy of third-party websites or third-party content originators.
5.     How We Share Information
       a.    Partners and Service Providers. We may provide collected
information to our business partners, clients, licensees, and service
providers. They may use your information to perform services for us
and advertise their products and services to you.
       b. Advertisers or Advertising Networks. We may provide
collected information (either alone or combined with information
provided by third-parties or public information) about users of the Site
on an aggregated, anonymous basis to our advertisers to help them reach
the kind of audience they want to target.
       c.    Law Enforcement and Safety. We may also share or
disclose your information to comply with a court order or other legal
obligation, to enforce the Site terms of use, and to protect the rights,
property or safety of our users and other third-parties. We may disclose
information to government or law enforcement officials or private
parties as we determine, in our sole and absolute discretion, is necessary
or appropriate to respond to claims or to comply with legal processes, to
comply with laws, regulations or ordinances or to prevent or stop
illegal, unethical or actionable activity.
       d. Business Transfer. In the event that the Site or the Company
(or its affiliates, subsidiaries or parent) undergoes a merger, acquisition
by another company or sale of its assets (including the Site), your
information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

6.    Opting-Out of Information Use
As described above, we collect personally identifiable information about
you when you voluntarily provide it to us, collect other information
about you and your use of the Site automatically when you interact with
us, and may combine the collected information with publicly available
information or information provided to us by third-parties or to build a
profile about you. If you do not want us to use your collected
information as described above or to provide your information to our
partners, clients or service providers for marketing purposes,
please email us: nick@ thissongissick.com with such request.
With respect to the Site’s use of cookies and other similar technologies,
by adjusting settings on your browser, you may elect not to allow
cookies to be placed, and thus opt out of certain features of the Site and
the Site’s automatic collection of certain information about you.
Additionally, the links below will assist you in opting-out of cookies and
online behavioral or interest-based advertising:
   • First-Party Opt-Out:
         o Visit Google: http://www.google.com/privacy/ads
         o Click “Ads Settings”
   • Third-Party and Online Behavioral Advertising Opt-Out
         o Please visit:
               § Digital Advertising Alliance Consumer Choice Page:
                 http://www.aboutads.info/choices
               § Network Advertising Initiative Consumer Opt-Out:
                 http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/
Please note that these measures are browser-specific and device-specific
and must be repeated on all browsers and devices.
7.    Protection of Information

We use reasonable measures to safeguard your information in our
possession. However, no data transmission over the Internet is
completely secure and no security mechanism is impenetrable.
Therefore, although we take steps to protect your information, we cannot
guarantee the security of the information that we collect from you or the
security of our servers or the Site. By accessing the Site, any
transmission of information is at your own risk and you agree to assume
all risk in connection with information sent to us or collected by us.
8.     User Contributions.
You are responsible for content that you contribute to be published or
displayed on the Site or transmit to other users of the Site (“User
Contributions”), if any. Your User Contributions are posted on and
transmitted to other users of the Site at your own risk. Additionally, we
cannot control the actions of other users of the Site with whom you may
choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do
not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by
unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any
privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You
understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of your
User Contributions may remain viewable in cached or archived pages or
might have been copied or stored by others.
9.     Foreign Jurisdiction.
The Site is designed for and targeted to United States audiences and are
governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the United
States. The Company is not responsible under any privacy laws or local
data protection laws in any jurisdiction other than the United States.
10.    Children and Parents.
We respect children’s privacy. We do not target or knowingly or
intentionally collect personally identifiable information from children

under the age of 13. By using the Site, you have represented and
warranted that you are either 18 years of age or using the Site with the
supervision of a parent or guardian. If you are under the age of 13, you
may not use the Site. If you become aware that your child has provided
us with personal information without your consent, please email
us. nick@thissongissick.com
If you are a California resident under the age of 18 and a registered user
of the Site, California Business and Professions Code Section 22581
permits you to request and obtain removal of content or information you
have publicly posted, including User Submissions. To make such a
request,      please    nick@thissongissick.COM        or     write     us
thissongissick.com Privacy Policy, 315 Park Avenue South, 16th
Floor New York, NY 10010, USA with a detailed description of the
specific content or information to be removed.
Please be aware that such a request does not ensure complete or
comprehensive removal of the content or information you have posted
(including User Submissions, if any) and that there may be
circumstances in which the law does not require or allow removal even
if requested.
11.   Your California Privacy Rights
If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83
permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your
personal information by the Company to third-parties for direct
marketing purposes. To make such a request, please email us or write us
at the California information noted below.
12.   Miscellaneous.
From time to time We may modify this Privacy Policy to reflect, among
other things, changes in the law or our information collection and use
practices and such modifications shall be effective upon posting by us.

Your continued use of the Site after a revised Privacy Policy signifies
your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. It is important that you
review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are updated as to
any changes.
13.   Contact Us.
If you have any general questions about this Privacy Policy or other
aspects of the Site please contact us at:
VaynerPublishing
Attention: thissongissick.com Privacy Policy
315 Park Avenue South, 16th Floor New York, NY 10010, USA or
Email: nick@thissongissick.com
If you are making a request related to your rights as a resident of
California, please contact us at:
VaynerPublishing
Attention: thissongissick.com California Privacy Rights
315 Park Avenue South, 16th Floor New York, NY 10010, USA or
Email: Contact@vaynerpublishing.com with Subject Line:
California Privacy Rights - thissongissick
You also may have the right (subject to certain exceptions) to be given a
copy of the information that we collects about you or to correct, update,
and/or      erase      that     information.     Please     email      us
contact@vaynerpublishing.com with any such request.
